gplus.com 2007-12-27

# Gplus Messenger: Google Talk Enchancer

**PRIVACY POLICY**

The purpose of this Gplus privacy policy is to inform you how Gplus treats personal information gathered about you when you visit Gplus.com, how we may use that information and the choices you have regarding the use and disclosure of such information.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Gplus does not own or control or to people that Gplus does not employ or manage.

**Privacy**  
Gplus respects your right to privacy and observes the provisions of the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable data protection laws.

Any details that you give to us via this website or in any other way may be added to our database. You do not have to give us any personal information in order to use most of this website. However, if you wish to take advantage of some of the more special personalised services that we may from time to time offer, you will need to provide certain information.

**Your consent**  
By using our website you consent, where applicable, to the collection and use of your personal information, such as your user name and ICP address, in the manner set out in this privacy policy. Gplus may also collect information such as your age, gender, and interests. If we change or modify this privacy policy we shall post these changes on this page.

**Use of Personal Details**  
Our database of personal details (however we collect these details) is used by us, and third parties acting on our behalf, for the following general purposes: providing the Gplus service, improving our services, contacting you, conducting research, customising the advertising and content you see, client administration and marketing related purposes.

If you choose to register for a service we may specifically ask you for additional information in order to provide that service to you. 

Gplus does not rent, sell or disclose your contact details to any other third party.

**Contacting us about your information**  
If you would like to see the information we hold about you or would like to be removed from our database, please contact us. 

To help us keep our database up-to-date, we would be grateful if you would let us know as soon as any of your contact details change or if you notice any inaccuracies in them. Please also let us know if you no longer wish to receive information or services from us.

**Cookies**  
We may use cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data which is stored on your computer's hard drive which makes it easier to identify you and which is revealed to us when you use this website. We also use cookies to track the interest of our users so that we can subsequently enhance their experience on our website. You can configure your web browser not to accept cookies, although this may affect how you see and are able to use this website.

We would be grateful if you would also let us know if you have any comments in relation to this site or have spotted any errors or non-functioning parts of the site. You can contact us.
